<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
   <string id="Antirad">
      <text>Antiradiation drugs</text>
   </string>
   <string id="Arm-heavy">
      <text>Heavy stalker gear</text>
   </string>
   <string id="Arm-light">
      <text>Light stalker gear</text>
   </string>
   <string id="Arm-medium">
      <text>Medium stalker gear</text>
   </string>
   <string id="bandage">
      <text>Bandages</text>
   </string>
   <string id="Binocul">
      <text>Binoculars</text>
   </string>
   <string id="Bread">
      <text>Bread</text>
   </string>
   <string id="cit_deadcity_maps_desc">
      <text>A detailed map of the Dead City including Merc positions</text>
   </string>
   <string id="cit_deadcity_maps_name">
      <text>Map of the Dead City</text>
   </string>
   <string id="cit_doctors_key_desc">
      <text>Doctor's key to the secret stash in Pripyat</text>
   </string>
   <string id="cit_doctors_key_short_desc">
      <text>Doctor's key</text>
   </string>
   <string id="Conserva">
      <text>Tourist's Delight</text>
   </string>
   <string id="Detect1">
      <text>Anomaly detector</text>
   </string>
   <string id="Devic">
      <text>Instruments and devices</text>
   </string>
   <string id="device-PDA">
      <text>PDA</text>
   </string>
   <string id="device-torch">
      <text>Flashlight</text>
   </string>
   <string id="device-torch_m1">
      <text>Super Flashlight</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_equipment_armors_arm-heavy">
      <text>Protective suit. Weight: 18kg. Details: Protects the body from Jelly, Burnt Fuzz, most anomalies and physical damage. The torso and back are protected by built-in bio-metallic plates. The suit is equipped with an airtight, reinforced plastic helmet and two oxygen bottles. Note: During extended periods of use the suit tears through and gradually deteriorates beyond use.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_equipment_armors_arm-light">
      <text>Protective suit. Weight: 8 kg. Details: Protects the body from weak anomalies and physical damage. Equipped with an oxygen mask. Note: During extended periods of use the suit tears through and gradually deteriorates beyond use.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_equipment_armors_arm-medium">
      <text>Protective suit. Weight: 12 kg. Details: Protects the user from Jelly, Burnt Fuzz, many anomalies and physical damage. Equipped with an airtight helmet and an oxygen bottle. Note: During extended periods of use the suit tears through and gradually deteriorates beyond use.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_equipment_armors_sci2">
      <text>A red S.C.A.P.E suit with an airtight helmet. Weight: 11kg. Description: Protects the body from fire, acid, toxic gas, various anomalies, Burnt Fuzz and physical damage. Equipped with two oxygen bottles. Note: During extended periods of use the suit tears through and gradually deteriorates beyond use.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_equipment_devic_binocul1">
      <text>Military field binoculars</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_equipment_devic_detect1">
      <text>A device for detecting anomaly fields and disturbances. Notifies of their presence with a sound. Needs to be attached to the belt and turned on to operate correctly.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_equipment_devic_detect2">
      <text>A device that detects and reports anomalous fields and disturbances with an audible signal.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_equipment_devic_detect3">
      <text>Elite anomaly detector invented by scientists in the Zone. It detects not only the presence of anomalous fields and disturbances, but also shows their location on a map and reports them with an audible signal.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_equipment_devic_detect4">
      <text>Anomaly detector used by the Monolith group. The technology behind its function is unknown. The advantages over the elite anomaly detector are the lighter weight of the device and the fact that it can also function as an artifact detector.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_equipment_devic_device-PDA1">
      <text>Personal digital assistant - indispensable in the Zone.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_equipment_devic_device-torch1">
      <text>A powerful flashlight. Quite useful in areas with insufficient lighting.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_equipment_devic_device-torch1_m1">
      <text>A powerful flashlight. Battery recharge time has been reduced thanks to a modernized transformer.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_equipment_energydrink">
      <text>Non Stop' is an excellent energy drink consisting of caffeine, taurine and a mixture of rejuvenating vitamins. Just the ticket when you're too tired to push forward!</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_equipment_food_bread1">
      <text>Hard to say who manages to bake these loaves in the Zone, but the bread isn't contaminated and is perfectly edible. Well, at least none of the stalkers have complained about it.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_equipment_food_conserva1">
      <text>Canned food from an army warehouse raided by stalkers. The best-before period hasn't expired yet.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_equipment_food_kolbasa1">
      <text>Made from a mix of chicken and soya, the "diet" sausage is often, for lack of other options, a stalker's breakfast, lunch and dinner in one.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_equipment_food_vodka1">
      <text>Vodka made by the NA company. Goes down easily and significantly reduces the effects of radiation, but for obvious reasons should be enjoyed in moderation.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_equipment_medi_antirad1">
      <text>Reduces the effects of radiation.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_equipment_medi_bandage1">
      <text>Bandages. Help stop bleeding.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_equipment_medi_medkit1">
      <text>An all-purpose medkit. Used to treat injuries of various types and severities - wounds, burns, poisonings, etc.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_equipment_medi_medkit2">
      <text>A specialized medical set to fight against physical damage and blood loss. In it is included a component for blood coagulation, antibiotics, immunal stimulators, and painkillers.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_equipment_medi_medkit3">
      <text>Medical set, designed especially for work in the Zone. The set includes means of healing wounds as well as means of eliminating radionucleodes from the body. Prevents the development of radiowave sickness and lowers the dose of accumulated radiation.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="energy_drink_name">
      <text>Non Stop' Energy drink</text>
   </string>
   <string id="energy_drink_short_name">
      <text>Non Stop' Energy drink</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_equipments_sleeping_bag">
      <text>Possibily the most of a camping equipment sent, the sleeping bag is obviously designed designed for rest and sleep. It provides good insulation against cold temperatures, as well as humidity.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_equipments_cat_bag">
      <text>This saber-toothed cat in a bag is trained to protect its owner. Weighs quite a bit, but can very effectively help to repel attacks of various types of evil. If necessary, the cat can be put into the bag again. Fragments of the artifact Spring are sewn into the lining of the bag to reduce the size of this large animal.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="Equipment">
      <text>Gear and food</text>
   </string>
   <string id="Food">
      <text>Food</text>
   </string>
   <string id="Kolbasa">
      <text>Diet sausage</text>
   </string>
   <string id="Medi">
      <text>Medicaments</text>
   </string>
   <string id="Medkit">
      <text>Medkit</text>
   </string>
   <string id="Medkit_army">
      <text>Army first aid kit</text>
   </string>
   <string id="Medkit_scientific">
      <text>Scientific first aid kit</text>
   </string>
   <string id="Sci2">
      <text>Scientific EXP-4</text>
   </string>
   <string id="Vodka">
      <text>Cossacks vodka</text>
   </string>
   <string id="st_detector1">
      <text>Dosimeter</text>
   </string>
   <string id="st_detector2">
      <text>Anomaly detector</text>
   </string>
   <string id="st_detector3">
      <text>Elite anomaly detector</text>
   </string>
   <string id="st_detector4">
      <text>Anomaly detector "Monolith"</text>
   </string>
   <string id="st_detector_descr">
      <text>Intended for the detection of anomalous zones as well as hotbeds of radioactive pollution.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="st_sleeping_bag">
      <text>Sleeping bag</text>
   </string>
   <string id="st_cat_bag">
      <text>Cat in a bag</text>
   </string>
   <string id="tre_ruck">
      <text>Empty backpack</text>
   </string>
   <string id="tre_ruck_s">
      <text>Empty backpack</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_tre_ruck">
      <text>Hiking backpack made of rubberized fabric with a camouflage pattern. It does not get wet and has hard to see if hidden properly. It is ideal for laying down your stash in a secluded place.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="kpb_name">
      <text>Electronic game</text>
   </string>
   <string id="kpb_desc">
      <text>One of the electronic toys that were so popular in the recent past.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="kittens_name">
      <text>Detector "Monolith"</text>
   </string>
   <string id="kittens_desc">
      <text>Anomaly and artifact detector used by the Monolith. The technology behind its function is unknown.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_pda_labx8_name">
      <text>PDA from X-8</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_pda_labx8_desc">
      <text>PDA with secret data from the laboratory X8.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_notebook_jupiter_name">
      <text>Portable Computer </text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_notebook_jupiter_desc">
      <text>Portable computer assistant from the scientific bunker near Jupiter. Contains important information.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_doc_jupiter_name">
      <text>Documents from Jupiter</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_doc_jupiter_desc">
      <text>Documentation with classified data from a lab near Jupiter.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_kubik_rubik_name">
      <text>Rubik's Cube</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_kubik_rubik_desc">
      <text>One of the most popular puzzle toys so far from the 1980s. It's inexpensive and weighs practically nothing. I don't see why anyone would be willing to pay a decent reward for it...</text>
   </string>
   <string id="Beer">
      <text>Beer</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_equipment_food_beer">
      <text>Baltic Beer. When enjoyed in small amounts, it restores some strength, but in excessive amounts it is intoxicating.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="Flaska">
      <text>Flask</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_equipment_food_flaska">
      <text>A flask with water.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="Naka">
      <text>Chocolate bar</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_equipment_food_naka">
      <text>Chocolate bar. A good snack when there's nothing else to eat.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="pripyat_key_name">
      <text>Key</text>
   </string>
   <string id="pripyat_key_desc">
      <text>A key that opens an unknown door...</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_floppy_disketka_name">
      <text>Floppy disk</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_floppy_disketka_desc">
      <text>A disk with data on secret military developments.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_music_cddisk_name">
      <text>Compact disk</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_music_cddisk_desc">
      <text>A compact disc with some supposedly important information.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_condensators_name">
      <text>Capacitors</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_condensators_desc">
      <text>Box of capacitors.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_transistors_name">
      <text>Transistors</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_transistors_desc">
      <text>Box of transistors.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_katushka_provoloki_name">
      <text>Coil of wire</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_katushka_provoloki_desc">
      <text>A coil of copper wire. Used to repair electrical wiring.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_icona_name">
      <text>Icon</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_icona_desc">
      <text>It's an old and very valuable icon. Collectors are willing to pay large sums for it.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="flower_ameliya_name">
      <text>Scarlet Flower</text>
   </string>
   <string id="flower_ameliya_desc">
      <text>The petals are white, with a bluish hue. The bud is large, cross-shaped. The flower has a pleasant fragrance. When you hold it in your hand, the Geiger counter stays quiet near radioactive zones. Apparently, the flower somehow absorbs most of the radiation. It also has other beneficial properties.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="container_rice_name">
      <text>Container with rice</text>
   </string>
   <string id="container_rice_desc">
      <text>A steel container designed to store various items under prolonged exposure to radiation. It's even possible to store food, without being afraid to receive a dose of radiation after consumption. The lid has a sticker labeled "Rice". The container is locked and a very tricky lock is built into it. Judging by the weight and the rattling sound while shaking, there's something inside.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="poison_gas_ballon_name">
      <text>Perin-B3 gas tank.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="poison_gas_ballon_desc">
      <text>A cylinder with a nerve-gas.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="liker_baileys_name">
      <text>Anomaly' Moonshine</text>
   </string>
   <string id="liker_baileys_desc">
      <text>A bottle of moonshine made by a forester in the Red Forest. It's allegedly brewed inside anomalies.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="box_cigara_name">
      <text>Box of cigars</text>
   </string>
   <string id="box_cigara_desc">
      <text>A box of Cuban 'Guantanamera' cigars.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_lekarstvo_name">
      <text>Medicine</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_lekarstvo_desc">
      <text>Strong pain killers.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="sigaret">
      <text>Cigarettes</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_sigaret_desc">
      <text>A pack of cigarettes. It is a marketable item in the Zone even among non-smoking stalkers, as cigarettes can be exchanged at a profit. They slightly quench the feeling of hunger, but are otherwise harmful to health.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="cigara">
      <text>Cigar</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_cigara_desc">
      <text>A cuban cigar. It is a commodity in the Zone even among non-smoking stalkers, as it can be sold for a modest sum of money. Slightly quench the feeling of hunger, but it is otherwise harmful to health.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="secret_device_name">
      <text>Psi Emitter</text>
   </string>
   <string id="secret_device_desc">
      <text>Portable device designed and assembled by Monolith scientists. The exact purpose is unknown, but the device is able to transmit a sufficiently strong psi radiation within a radius of up to 200 meters. It looks pretty dull, but the appearance is most likely deceptive.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="oreshki">
      <text>Peanuts</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_oreshki_desc">
      <text>Peanuts. Very nourishing and nutritious. They are expensive and rare.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="ryba">
      <text>Sprat</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_ryba_desc">
      <text>Ordinary canned sprats in tomato sauce. They are pretty common in the Zone, as hardly anyone outside the Zone eats them.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="Vitamin">
      <text>Vitamins</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_equipment_vitamin">
      <text>A daily dose of vitamins developed by scientists in the Zone specifically to reduce the harmful effects of radiation and anomalies. Restore strength, health and appetite, and temporarily increase the carry weight by an average of 1 kg.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="Herkules">
      <text>Hercules</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_equipment_herkules">
      <text>Concentrated food with creatine. Nutritious, and also very easy to use and store thanks to its compact size and light weight. It regenerates the stamina well and temporarily increases the portable weight by an average of 10 kg.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="repair_kit">
      <text>Repair kit</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_equipment_repair_kit">
      <text>A set of tools and devices for repairing cars during travels.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="Barrel">
      <text>Barrel</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_case_pred_name">
      <text>Documents from Outskirts</text>
   </string>
   <string id="explosive_charge_name">
      <text>Explosives</text>
   </string>
   <string id="explosive_charge_desc">
      <text>Clockwork explosives.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_note_jupiter_name">
      <text>Note from Jupiter</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_note_jupiter_desc">
      <text>A note with classified data from a lab near Jupiter.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_note_zaton_name">
      <text>Documents from Zaton</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_note_zaton_desc">
      <text>Documents with classified information, lost by the military expedition in Zaton.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_kanifol_name">
      <text>Rosin</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_kanifol_desc">
      <text>Box of rosin.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_textolite_name">
      <text>Textolite</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_textolite_desc">
      <text>Electric insulating structural material.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_memory_module_name">
      <text>Transformer</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_memory_module_desc">
      <text>A device with an electrotechnical purpose.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_toolkit_1_name">
      <text>Tools</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_toolkit_1_desc">
      <text>A basic set of tools.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_toolkit_2_name">
      <text>Tools</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_toolkit_2_desc">
      <text>A set of tools for fine work.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_toolkit_3_name">
      <text>Tools</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_toolkit_3_desc">
      <text>A set of tools for extremely precise work.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_black_box_name">
      <text>Black Box</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_black_box_desc">
      <text>The black box of the helicopter that crashed over the Dead Marshes.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_pda_lucky_name">
      <text>Owl</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_pda_lucky_desc">
      <text>Some incomprehensible device, which according to scientists allegedly emits shot distance frequencies, which scare away some monsters. It is ineffective against monsters capable of attacking at distances exceeding the range of the device. It is powered by a specific and still unknown type of energy that is present in the Zone. The device discharges quite quickly, but afterwards it starts to accumulate this unknown energy again. It is mounted in the anomaly detector slot.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_pda_tiran_name">
      <text>Calculator</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_pda_tiran_desc">
      <text>An ordinary scientific calculator.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_msl_pda_name">
      <text>Electronic card</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_msl_pda_desc">
      <text>An electronic access card from some secret vault in Pripyat.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="container_green_name">
      <text>Green container</text>
   </string>
   <string id="container_green_desc">
      <text>A steel container designed to store various items under prolonged exposure to radiation. It's even possible to store food, without being afraid to receive a dose of radiation after consumption. The lid has a sticker labeled "Green". The container is locked and a very tricky lock is built into it. Judging by the weight and the rattling sound while shaking, there's something inside.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_predatel_card_name">
      <text>Traitor ID</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_predatel_card_desc">
      <text>ID of the Duty traitor.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_playboy_name">
      <text>Magazine</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_playboy_desc">
      <text>It's a very fascinating magazine.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="st_id_simple">
      <text>Detector "Echo"</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_id_simple">
      <text>Outdated first-generation anomalous activity detector model. Emits a light signal as it approaches anomalies. It can also detect the presence of artifacts and measure the distance to the nearest artifact. The distance to the artifact is determined by the frequency of the light signal. For the sake of reliability, the readings should be taken while standing still.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="st_id_advanced">
      <text>Detector 'Scout'</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_id_advanced">
      <text>Second generation anomalous activity detector. Equipped with an anomaly locator and LED board to display the direction to the artifact and the distance to it.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="st_id_elite">
      <text>Detector 'Search'</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_id_elite">
      <text>Third-generation detector-scanner used by scientists. Thanks to three independent detectors, the approximate position of an artifact relative to the detector is shown on a special screen.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="st_id_elite_plus">
      <text>Prototype detector 'Svarog'</text>
   </string>
   <string id="enc_id_elite_plus">
      <text>Anomalous zone scanner prototype with extended functionality. Added a program to recognize static zones of scientifically known anomalous activity, while maintaining the ability to detect artifacts. The location of the anomalous zones and artifacts relative to the detector are displayed on a special screen. The detector is also capable of transmitting the coordinates of the detected anomalies to the GPS navigator if there is a wireless connection available.</text>
   </string>
	<string id="st_drug_coagulant">
		<text>Vinca</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_drug_coagulant_descr">
		<text>Ukrainian Vikasolum - an artificial equivalent of vitamin K. The main purpose of this drug is to increase blood coagulation speed. In great demand among stalkers who want slow-healing wounds and lacerations inflicted by mutants to close up faster. The effects of the drug are long-lasting.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_drug_psy_blockade">
		<text>Psi-Block</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_drug_psy_blockade_descr">
		<text>A drug that blocks avalanche-like nerve impulses. Consumption induces short-term loss of all emotion. Used exclusively in the Zone to counteract the effects of anomalous psy-fields. The effects of the drug are long-lasting.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_drug_radioprotector">
		<text>Radioprotectant</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_drug_radioprotector_descr">
		<text>B190 Indraline radioprotectant, included in medkits issued to nuclear power plant personnel. Used in the Zone instead of the excessively toxic PC1 cystamine hydrochloride, repeated use of which often caused death. Reduces the effects of gamma radiation on live tissue. Best consumed before exposure, as effects are not instant. The effects of the drug are long-lasting.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_dar_pass_flash_name">
      <text>Transmitter</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_dar_pass_flash_desc">
      <text>A device for transmitting and receiving signals between two different communication environments.</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_evm_name">
      <text>Computer</text>
   </string>
   <string id="item_evm_desc">
      <text>Favorite electronic computer of Associate Professor Dudurov.</text>
   </string>
</string_table>